<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days Of Wellness</string>
    <string name="title_day_1">Rev your metabolism with a glass of lemon water.</string>
    <string name="description_day_1">Supercharge your day, get your metabolism fired up, and wake up your digestion with a glass of warm lemon water and a pinch of cayenne pepper. Sip on this before you hit play on your morning FitOn workout, or before you sit down for breakfast.</string>
    <string name="title_day_2">Add a superfood to all of your meals.</string>
    <string name="description_day_2">Want to supercharge all of your meals with little to no effort? Simply add one superfood to each of your meals today. Try adding chia or hemp seeds to your morning bowl of oatmeal, avocado to your smoothie, and cilantro to your taco bowls.</string>
    <string name="title_day_3">Try a green smoothie.</string>
    <string name="description_day_3">Ready to amp up your smoothie game? Try a green smoothie today by blending up your usual smoothie recipe with the addition of a handful or two of dark leafy greens. Blend, sip and nourish your body.</string>
    <string name="title_day_4">Do a 20-minute strength training workout.</string>
    <string name="description_day_4">Build some strength today with a FitOn 20-minute strength training workout. Get out of your comfort zone a bit and use those dumbbells you’ve been meaning to add to your fitness routine or grab the resistance bands. Your muscles will thank you later.</string>
    <string name="title_day_5">Switch up your evening routine.</string>
    <string name="description_day_5">If you don’t have a wind-down period where you destress before bed, try switching up your evening routine by trying something new. Take an Epsom salt bath with lavender essential oils, try 10 minutes of meditation, or close out Instagram and read a book instead. Do something to help your mind and body wind down and relax before bed for a better night sleep.</string>
    <string name="title_day_6">Make a workout playlist &amp; get moving!.</string>
    <string name="description_day_6">Stuck in a workout rut and can’t quite find the motivation to get your exercise in? Make a workout playlist that will motivate you to get your body moving. Better yet, make a playlist, and then get a 15 minute HIIT workout in while you’re at it. Sometimes the hardest part is starting. So get your music playing and get going. We promise, you’ll never regret a workout, you’ll only regret the ones you didn’t find time to fit in.</string>
    <string name="title_day_7">Schedule in a day of self-care.</string>
    <string name="description_day_7">Have you pushed off all of your self-care appointments lately? Here’s your invitation to take a look at your schedule and book that overdue hair appointment, or use that massage gift card that’s been sitting in your bag since last year. Get something in the books, and commit because self-care should never be optional.</string>
    <string name="title_day_8">Do a quick HIIT workout.</string>
    <string name="description_day_8">Get a quick HIIT workout in today in between all the things you need to get done. The great thing about HIIT is that you can work up a sweat and burn calories in as little as 15 minutes. Plus, FitOn makes it easy to get your workouts in anywhere and any time since our classes are always open.</string>
    <string name="title_day_9">Read a book.</string>
    <string name="description_day_9">You know that book you’ve been meaning to read but haven’t had the chance to? Today’s the day to find the time to take ten minutes to just open the book and get started. Read a few pages before bed or when you are enjoying your morning cup of coffee. Who knows, maybe this will become a new routine for you!</string>
    <string name="title_day_10">Listen to a Podcast or Audiobook.</string>
    <string name="description_day_10">Are podcasts or audiobooks more your speed? Press play on a podcast you love or listen to an audiobook on your way to work. Pick something that will brighten your mood or add some motivation to your day!</string>
    <string name="title_day_11">Practice Saying No.</string>
    <string name="description_day_11">For many of us, we have a habit of saying yes to just about everything. This can quickly lead to overwhelm and not leave any room in our schedule for the things that really matter. Say no at least once today to something that doesn’t serve you or fit into the season of life you are currently in. When you say no, you say yes to more time for self-care. And, if saying no is something that’s really hard for you, the more you do it, the better you get, and the less guilty you feel about thinking you are letting others down.</string>
    <string name="title_day_12">Do a 10-minute stretch.</string>
    <string name="description_day_12">Open your FitOn app and do a 10-minute stretch to help relax tight muscles, calm the mind, and prepare your body for tomorrow’s workout.</string>
    <string name="title_day_13">Try Tabata.</string>
    <string name="description_day_13">After a day of stretching you’re ready for something a little higher intensity. Try a tabata workout to scorch calories, build strength, and get the blood flowing. FitOn offers a hardcore Tabata workout that you can get done in under 15 minutes with trainer Breann Mitchell. All you need is a mat and a positive attitude, and you’ll be in and out and feeling amazing in no time.</string>
    <string name="title_day_14">Stop and breathe!</string>
    <string name="description_day_14">When we’re stressed, so many of us hold our breath and tense up. Unfortunately, this is actually totally counterproductive and will only cause more tension in the body. Today, make it your goal to be more mindful of your breath and how you are holding your body when you feel stressed. If you find yourself tensing up, stop and breathe! Take a few cleansing breaths, and see how much more relaxed you feel afterward.</string>
    <string name="title_day_15">Make a healthy recipe.</string>
    <string name="description_day_15">Have you had your eye on a cookbook or have been planning to make that healthy recipe but just haven’t gotten around to it? Yup, this happens to us all, but tonight, commit to making a healthy recipe at home. It doesn’t have to be anything fancy. Pick something that has some veggies, fresh herbs, and spices, and something the whole family can enjoy. Maybe make a homemade pizza with cauliflower crust, tacos wrapped in lettuce leaves, or a veggie stir fry.</string>
    <string name="title_day_16">Cool down with a 20-minute yoga routine.</string>
    <string name="description_day_16">Relax your mind and your body with a 20-minute yoga routine. FitOn offers various yoga routines that will fit anyone’s lifestyle. From simple flow to yoga core, FitOn has all of your yoga needs covered. Plus, all you really need is 20 minutes to get your mind and your body centered for a more productive day.</string>
    <string name="title_day_17">Make plans with a friend.</string>
    <string name="description_day_17">If it seems like it’s been ages since you’ve gone out and caught up with your girlfriends, take today to schedule in a time to meet with a friend. Plan that long overdue coffee date, or make a plan to watch next week’s Bachelorette episode together with a glass of red wine in hand.</string>
    <string name="title_day_18">Get outside.</string>
    <string name="description_day_18">Make a point to get outside today! Get out and soak up some much-needed vitamin D, even if it’s only during 10 minutes of your lunch break. It’s far too common for us to get stuck in a rut being inside for nearly all hours of the day. Get out and enjoy the fresh air for a little bit today. You would be amazed at what this can do for your overall mood.</string>
    <string name="title_day_19">Do something that scares you.</string>
    <string name="description_day_19">Challenge yourself to do something that scares you today. Get out of your comfort zone because let’s face it, progress doesn’t happen there! Go to a kickboxing class, or ask for that raise you deserved years ago. Do something that pushes you outside of your comfort zone. The more you do this, the more comfortable it will become.</string>
    <string name="title_day_20">Organize one spot in your home.</string>
    <string name="description_day_20">Living a more minimalist lifestyle can significantly help improve your productivity simply by removing unnecessary clutter and distractions. Focus on one area in your home to declutter today, even if it’s just your dining room table which may seem to be your catch-all spot for unopened mail and anything and everything else. Starting with one spot may quickly motivate you to do this with other areas of your house.</string>
    <string name="title_day_21">Get out for a walk.</string>
    <string name="description_day_21">Go for a walk today! Bring your dog, call a friend to join, or just go by yourself to decompress, get the body moving, and breathe in some fresh air.</string>
    <string name="title_day_22">Add more healthy fats to your meals.</string>
    <string name="description_day_22">Fats are the bomb-at least the healthy fats like avocados, coconuts, nuts, and seeds. The body needs fat for things like hormone balance, brain health, and energy. So, don’t be afraid to add some healthy fats to your diet, and challenge yourself to add one fat to each meal today.</string>
    <string name="title_day_23">Practice one random act of kindness.</string>
    <string name="description_day_23">Sometimes paying it forward is all we need to feel better while also brightening someone else’s day. The world needs more kindness, so practice one random act of kindness today. Maybe buy a coffee for the person behind you in the drive-thru line at Starbucks, or simply hold the door for a mom who has her hands full with kiddos and grocery bags. Trust us, finding the time to go out of your way to be kind to someone helps everyone, including you!</string>
    <string name="title_day_24">Wake up 30 minutes earlier.</string>
    <string name="description_day_24">While this may be the last thing you want to do, give it a try for one day! Try waking up 30 minutes earlier to get a few things done for you. You may find that a little extra time in the morning allows you to carve out a “power half hour” to get a quick FitOn workout in, blend up a healthy smoothie, and set your intentions for a kick-butt day.</string>
    <string name="title_day_25">Unplug for two hours.</string>
    <string name="description_day_25">Commit to unplugging for two whole hours. While it may seem crazy to shut off your phone and not look at your Instagram or Facebook feed for a couple of hours, see what staying away from social media can do for your mental health. Try shutting off your phone, and doing something else to take care of you. You may find that your focus improves, you get more done, and you just feel more productive.</string>
    <string name="title_day_26">Strengthen the body with 20-minutes of Pilates.</string>
    <string name="description_day_26">We challenge you to try 20 minutes of Pilates today to strengthen your body and get your mind right. Try one of Cassey Ho’s FitOn Pilates workouts that will challenge you but also allow you to enjoy and have fun with your workout.</string>
    <string name="title_day_27">Plan your next vacation.</string>
    <string name="description_day_27">If it’s been far too long since you’ve really unplugged and gone on vacation, think about and even plan out your next trip. Even if it’s unrealistic for you to get away until next year, you can at least start planning. It will give you something to look forward to!</string>
    <string name="title_day_28">Get the blood flowing with a 30-minute cardio workout.</string>
    <string name="description_day_28">You are almost at the end of the 30-day wellness challenge, which means you are stronger than you were before you started and ready to kick your workouts up a notch. Challenge yourself by getting the blood pumping and those endorphins flowing with a FitOn 30-minute cardio workout. Both your health and mood will thank you for it later.</string>
    <string name="title_day_29">Reassess your goals.</string>
    <string name="description_day_29">Did you set some new years goals at the start of the year, but haven’t really sat down to address where you’re at with reaching them? Take the time today to reassess your goals, and adjust where needed.</string>
    <string name="title_day_30">Stop the negative self-talk for an entire day.</string>
    <string name="description_day_30">We are often our own worst critic, and we can really say some pretty harmful things to ourselves. Today, stop all the negative self-talk. If you wouldn’t say it to a friend, don’t say it to yourself. When you eliminate the “I can’t” or the “I’m not good enough” talk, you get out of your own way and can really start working towards your goals and the healthy and happy life you deserve!</string>
    <string name="wellness_planner">Wellness Planner</string>

</resources>